Littauer Library Collection of Miscellaneous Union Files 5964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- King, Carol. (Labor Lawyer, New York City) Collection. Includes briefs, correspondence, and related documents. 1930's. (Box 14)
  - Injunction Case Cinderella Theater Co. (Detroit) - Sign Writer's Local 591, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Closed Shop, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Injunctions - General, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Misc. folder, booklets, and papers
  - Civil Liberties, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Misc. booklets and papers
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1932-1935 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Boycotting and Blacklisting (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Breach of Contract, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- United States Emergency Boards. 74, 75, 78 - 1949. Railroad cases. (Box 15)
  - Eastern Railways Miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board Transcript, April and May, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    2 booklets
  - Emergency Board Transcript, May 2-3 1949 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Board Transcript, April and September, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Board Report and Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Maps Showing Route of Hot Metal, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Advertisement and Assignment Forms, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Map Showing Track Purchases, 1927-1948 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Map Showing Track Purchases and Sales, 1930-1948 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Map Showing Track Sales at Bessemer, 1943-1948 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Exhibits for Emergency Board, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Board Transcript, June 20-21 1949 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1 Ex Parte Submission, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2 Ex Parte Submission, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - June, July, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - June 22, 29, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 15, 19, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 20, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - April, June, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    2 booklets, map
  - Emergency Board Transcript - April, September, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - September 26-27, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - September 22-23, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 8, 11, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Monongahela Connecting Railroad Co., 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Misc. papers and map
- United States Emergency Boards. 74, 75, 78 - 1949. Railroad cases. (Box 16)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 6-7, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - June, July, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - June 24, July 5, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum and Maps, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Maps and misc. papers
  - Map and Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - May, July, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 12, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - July 13, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board Transcript - September, October, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    3 booklets
  - Carrier Exhibit, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Railroad Records, 1947-1949 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Misc. papers, photos
  - Miscellaneous Maps, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    8 maps
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - The Gazette and Telegraph Co., 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - National War Labor Board, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Various Arbitration Awards, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Agreements, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Articles of Agreement, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Horowitz, Daniel (Professor) Harvard University. Papers regarding labor, 1940's. Includes arbitration papers, National Labor Relations Board documents, correspondence, agreements, etcetera. (Box 17)
  - Articles of Agreement/Post War Educational Policy, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Folder, booklet, misc. papers
  - After the War, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Misc. papers, booklets, envelope
  - Colt's Patent Fire Arms MFG. Co., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    2 envelopes
  - LA Union Passenger Terminal, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Postal Employees, National Alliance of, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mine Workers, United, District 50, Gas, By-Product, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1921-1941 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Hosiery Workers, American Federation of (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Plasterers and Cement Finishers International Association, Operative, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Cleaners and Dyers Union, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Manpower, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Interviews, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Various Agreements, 1939-1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Post Office Clerks, National Federation of, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Railway Agreements, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Plate Glass Companies, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - National War Labor Board Reports, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Millinery Industry, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Outlines, 1939-1942 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Agreements, 1936-1943 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Misc. booklets
  - Union Agreements, 1935-1941 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Collective Agreements, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Horowitz, Daniel (Professor) Harvard University. Papers regarding labor, 1940's. Includes arbitration papers, National Labor Relations Board documents, correspondence, agreements, etcetera. (Box 18)
  - Union Agreements, 1935-1942 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - War Cases, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National War Labor Board - Legal, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Office of War Information, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National War Labor Board Proceedings, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wages, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Regional and National War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Wages Continued, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Retail Grocery and Food Store Employees' Union, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Longshoremen's Board Arbitration Award, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Award of the Federal Arbitrator, Various Ports, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "Steam Schooner Awards" 1937-1941 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Brief of Waterfront Employers Association of San Francisco, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Ship Clerks and Waterfront Employers, Volume 1-2, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    2 packets
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Ship Clerks and Waterfront Employers, Volume 3-4, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Ship Clerks and Waterfront Employers, Volume 5-6, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Ship Clerks and Waterfront Employers, Volume 7-8, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Arbitrator's Oral Decision - Portland, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration - San Francisco, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Misc. papers and packets
  - Arbitrator's Award, Pacific Coast, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Ship Clerks' Union, Longshoremen, Waterfront Employers Proceedings, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Packet
  - Arbitrator's Award - Longshoremen and Waterfront Employers, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Arbitration Awards. Longshoreman and Warehousemen's Union, West Coast, 1934-1942. (Box 19)
  - Arbitrator's Award - Portland, San Francisco, Pacific Coast, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Misc. papers and packet
  - Arbitrator's Award and Final Decision, Portland, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Proceedings between International Longshoremen and Waterfront Employers, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrator's Award Concerning Various Controversies, San Francisco, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Packets
  - Arbitrator's Award, Waterfront Employers, International Longshoremen, Tacoma, Washington (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Longshoremen's Labor Relation Board, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Waterfront Employers of Washington and Longshoremen, Arbitrator's Award, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Misc. packets
  - 1941 Wage Arbitration, Ar and Waterfront Employers, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Arbitrator's Award 1941, Waterfront Employers and Longshoremen (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen and Waterfront Employers - San Francisco, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Arbitrator's Award - Waterfront Employers of So. California and Marine Clerks, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Awards, Rehearings, and Clarifications, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Mediator's Recommendations, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Waterfront Employers and Longshoremen, Long Beach, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Hearing on Arbitration Before Irvin Stalmaster, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Scrap Metal Controversy, Arbitrator's Award, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Albert A. Rosenshine, Arbitrator's Award, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Matters, San Francisco and Pacific Coast, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Matters, Washington, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Statement and Award, Washington/Oregon, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Statement and Award, California, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Arbitration Awards. Longshoreman and Warehousemen's Union, West Coast, 1934-1942. (Box 20)
  - Arbitration Matters, Waterfront Employers and Longshoremen, 1935-1940 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union - Decisions (Morse), 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, M.C. Sloss, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Lift Boards, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Port of San Francisco, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, Partial Transcript, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lift Boards Arbitration, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration - Seattle and San Francisco, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, San Francisco June 27-28 1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, San Francisco, July 6-7 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, San Francisco, July 6, 8, 10 1939 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration - Dispatchers, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration - "Point Ancha", 1939 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Matters, Opening Reply/Argument for the Association, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration - Alleged Rights, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration - Stoppage of Work and Refusal to Cross Picket Line, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Misc. paper and 2 booklets
  - Arbitration - Discharge of Gunnies, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration - Sling Loads and Failure to Employ, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration - Preferred Gangs, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Arbitrator Decision, Portland, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Misc. papers, booklet, folder
  - Arbitration - Right to be Represented, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration - Disputes and Allegations, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Oral Decision - Alleged Spies, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration - Employer Right to use Preferred Gangs, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Penalties, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration - Refusal to go through Picket Line, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Arbitration Awards. Longshoreman and Warehousemen's Union, West Coast, 1934-1942. (Box 21)
  - Harry Hazel, Arbitrator for Port of Seattle, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Award, Related to Methods of Hiring/Dispatching, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - M.C. Sloss, Arbitrator for Pacific Coast Ports, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Interpretation of the Award of the National Longshoremen Board, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, Refusal of Longshoremen, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1941 Wage Arbitration, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Wage Adjustment Volume 4-5, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Wage Adjustment Volume 6, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 1941 Wage Arbitration, Brief of the Employers (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1941 Wage Arbitration before Wayne L. Morse, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 1941 Wage Arbitration/Arbitrator's Award, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Travel Time, San Pedro, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Volumes 1-2, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 3, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 15-16, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 7-8, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 18-19, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sulphur Handling, Port of Everett, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Daily Checkers Agreement, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Award, Stoppage of Work, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 9-10, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 18, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Longshoremen's Wage Adjustment, Vol. 12, 14, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Refusal to Cross Joint Picket Line, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Dispute, Refusal of Men to Work Lumber Cargo, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, Right to Transfer Gangs, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration, Miscellaneous, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Arbitration Materials - Printing Pressmen, 1920's-1940's. (Box 22)
  - Arbitration, Holiday Pay, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Misc. folders
  - Arbitration, Wages, Hours, Duration of Contract, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, New Contract, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    2 folders
  - Arbitration of Vacations with Pay, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Appeal Proceeding Before International Arbitration Board, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Appeal From Award of Local Board, Chicago, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, Manning of Presses, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Award, New Contract, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration, Manning of Presses, 1933-1937 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration, Wage Scales, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration, Manning of Press, Indianapolis and Chicago, 1937-1940 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Folders
  - Brief, New Contract - Houston, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Award, Wages, Hours, and Term of Contract, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration, Galveston, Tex., 1926-1927 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Proceedings, Manning of Presses, Indianapolis News, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Briefs, Manning of Presses at Indianapolis News, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rebuttal Brief, New Contract, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Proceedings, Wages - Detroit, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Award, New Contract - Cleveland, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration, Wages, etc. - Detroit, 1935-1939 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Briefs, Wage Scales - Dallas, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Proceedings, Wages, etc. - Indianapolis, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Award, Hours, Wages, Contract, Presses - Indianapolis, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Report of Proceedings, Hours, Wages - Indianapolis, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Proceedings, Wages - Boston, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Award, New Contract - Houston, 1935-1936 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration, Wages, Duration of Contract - Detroit, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Briefs, Union's Motion - Chicago, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Appeal Brief, Chicago, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Arbitration Materials - Printing Pressmen, 1920's-1940's. (Box 23)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 1-2), New Contract, etc. - Atlanta, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 3-4), Wages, etc. - Atlanta, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Award and Brief, Wages, etc. - Atlanta, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, Manning of Presses - Indianapolis, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Award and Appeal, Baltimore, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, Mid West, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Appeals, Baltimore, 1935-1939 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Brief and Award, Wages, etc. - Akron, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 1-2), Wages - Boston, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 3-4), Wages - Boston, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Wages, etc. - Atlanta, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 1-2), Contract, etc. - Baltimore, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 3), Interpretation - Baltimore, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 5), Wages - Boston, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Pima Facie Brief, Wages, etc. - Boston, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 6-7), Wage Scales - Boston, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 1), Manning, etc. - Chattanooga, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Award, Wages - Boston, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Proceedings, Contract - Chattanooga, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 4), Interpretation - Baltimore, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Proceedings (Vol. 4), Wages, etc. - Chattanooga, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Proceedings, Appeal - Chattanooga, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Prima Facie Brief, Arbitrable Issues - Chicago, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Briefs, Arbitrable Issues - Chicago, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Award, Arbitrable Issues, etc. - Chicago, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Materials - Detroit, City of. Firefighters. 1970. (Box 24)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 1), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Binder
  - Arbitration (Vol. 6), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 8), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 13), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Materials - Detroit, City of. Firefighters. 1970. (Box 25)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 4), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 5), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 15), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 11-12), Labor Contract - Detroit, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 16), Labor Contract - Detroit (Part 1), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration (Vol. 16), Labor Contract - Detroit (Part 2), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Award of Arbitrator, Pacific Coast Ports - San Francisco, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Matters, Pacific Coast Ports - Seattle, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Misc. papers and 2 booklets
  - Arbitration Matters, Pacific Coast, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration, Increased Wages, Longshoremen and Waterfront Employers, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration, Pacific Coast - California, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Maritime Industry Board, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Union Brief, Reply, Appeal, Arbitration Issues - Chicago, 1932-1933 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Proceedings - Chicago, 1933-1940 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Briefs, Wage Scales - Cincinnati, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    4 booklets
  - Publisher's Brief, Manning of Presses - Chicago, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Briefs, Wages, etc. - Cincinnati, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 26)
  - 168 27-RC-2268 Ward Transport Inc. L 961, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - L 170 A-B, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - L 170 C, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - L 170 D-H, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - L 170 I-P, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - L 170 Q-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 20 437 Toledo Paper Stock, Toledo, Ohio, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 477 Agreement File, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 494 A-Z, 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Local #504, 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 504, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Local 504, Agreement Files, etc., 1954-1958 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Local 504 cont., 1953-1967 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Agreement Files of Local 504, 1951-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Local 504, More Agreement Files, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Local 504, More Agreement Files cont., 1952-1958 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - L 398 127, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - L 122 A-Z, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 27)
  - L 82 A-Z, 1957-1959 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Misc. papers (large folder)
  - L 59, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - L 59 P, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - L 59 E-L, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - L 59 A-D, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 16, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - L 526 Agreement File, 1957-1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - L 646, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 28)
  - 1 Agreement Files, L 42, 1964-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 2 Agreement Files, L 42, 1959-1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 3 Agreement Files, L 42, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 4 Agreement Files, L 42, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 5 Agreement Files, L 42, 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 6 Agreement Files, L 42, 1954-1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 7 Agreement Files, L42, 1952-1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 8 Agreement Files, L 42, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 9 Agreement Files, L 42, 1960-1965 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 1 Agreement Files, L 25, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 2 Agreement Files, L 25, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - 3 Agreement Files, L 25, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - 4 Agreement Files, L 25, 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - 5 Agreement Files, L 25, 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - 6 Agreement Files, L 25, 1961-1964 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - L 49 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Agreement Files, L 397, 1961-1966 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 29)
  - L 526 C, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - L 404 A-C, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - L 404 S-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - L 437 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - L 504 M-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - L 504 C, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - L 504 D-L, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - L 496, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - L 504 A-B, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - L 404 I-M, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - L 404 N-R, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - L 646 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - L 735, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 30)
  - L 404 D-H, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - L 259 A-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - L 379 A-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - L 686, 1965-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - L 829 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - L 841, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1 Agreement Files, L 526, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 2 Agreement Files, L 526, 1965-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 3 Agreement Files, L 526, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Local 526 (A-B), 1958-1970 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - L 526 T-Z, 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 31)
  - Local 910, 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Local 926, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Local 911, 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Local 951, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Local 900, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Local 883, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Local 882, 1958-1965 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - L 841, 1962-1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - L 735, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - L 379, 1953-1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Local 962, 1959-1963 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Local 985, 1956-1961 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 1 Agreement Files, Local 379, 1957-1965 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 2 Agreement Files, Local 379, 1955-1967 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - 3 Agreement Files, Local 379, 1950-1960 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - 1 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1955-1963 (Box 31, Folder 16)